http://www.esl.org/about-us/policies/privacy

Skip To Content
Sign In
Online Banking User Login
Personal
Trouble Signing In?
Locations
Resources & ToolsABA# 222371863CalculatorsFeesFAQsFormsRatesBusiness SupportEducational ResourcesLife EventsVideosHoliday Hours
Careers
Customer Service
585.336.1000 800.848.2265 Mon to Fri: 7 a.m.-7 p.m. ET Sat: 8:30 a.m.-2 p.m. ET TEL-E$L Available 24/7
Personal
Why Choose ESL?
Additional Cards
Loans Auto & Leisure VehiclesHome EquityPersonal LoansShort-Term LoanMortgages Mortgage SolutionsPurchaseRefinanceFind a Mortgage OriginatorCash ServicesOnline Banking Services Mobile BankingOnline BankingChat Banking
Resources & Tools
Rates
Fees
Calculators
Educational Resources
Forms
FAQs
Sign in to Online Banking
Commercial
Why Choose ESL?
Business Membership
Checking
Savings
Credit Cards
Business Loans
Online Business Services
Resources & Tools
Experienced Team
Sign in to Online Banking
How Can We Help You?
Commercial
Why Choose ESL?
Checking
Savings
Commercial Lending
Cash Management
Fraud Prevention Solutions
Payable Solutions
Receivable Solutions
Online Banking
Trust Services
Why Choose ESL Investment Services, LLC?
Education Planning
Insurance Planning
Retirement Planning
Wealth Management Planning
Financial Planning
Estate Planning
Tax Advantaged Planning
Investment & Planning for Businesses & Corporations
Trust Services
Why Choose ESL Trust Services?
Trust Administration Services
Investment Management
Wealth Transfer Planning
Estate Planning and Administration Services
Resources & Tools
Experienced Team
Establishing a Trust
Trusts at a Glance
Events
ESL Charitable Foundation Meet Our TeamESL Extra VolunCare Crew
About Us
About Us
ESL Membership
Personal Membership
Business Membership
The ESL Difference
Your Everything Bank
Commitment to Service
Board Members
Convenient Banking BranchesTelephone BankingChat BankingPersonal Mobile BankingOnline BankingATMsTEL-ESLContactless PaymentHoliday HoursHistoryCareersESL Corporate Information
Fraud & Security FraudSecurityReport PhishingPolicies Equal Opportunity EmploymentPrivacySocial MediaWebsite AccessibilityDisclosures Personal DisclosuresBusiness DisclosuresInvestments DisclosuresCustomer Service
Financial Wellness
Financial Wellness
Becoming Financially Well
Personal Finance
Life Events
Meet Our Partners
Business SupportCalculators
Careers
Resources & Tools
ABA# 222371863
Calculators
Fees
FAQs
Forms PersonalBusinessInvest and PlanRatesBusiness Support Educational Resources Building CreditFinancial Tips for StudentsGetting a MortgageHELOAN vs HELOCHow to Build Your Homebuying TeamHow to Find a ContractorHSA Tax AdvantagesIdentity Theft Internet Security Living on a Reduced IncomeMoney ManagementPaying Down DebtPay Off Debt and Save Money Protect Against FraudRising RatesRetirement PlanningSafe Holiday ShoppingSavingSavings in Home RenovationsSmart Saving HabitsThe Right Savings AccountUnderstanding the Prime RateWays to Pay Down DebtWhat is a Credit Score What to Know About a Home Equity Loan
Life Events Buying a CarFresh StartGrowing FamilyPreparing to Buy a HomeSaving for Goals or EmergenciesSaving and Paying for CollegeSaving for RetirementSaying GoodbyeEnjoying RetirementYoung SaversVideosHoliday Hours
ESL Live Chat Banking
Did You Know...
Live Chat is not only for questions, but also for online banking! Additional informational message about online banking can go here
Information about live chat
More information can go here
Even more content can be listed
Maybe there's a link at the end
Third Party Site
For your convenience esl.org provides a variety of information on our website that is not directly related to ESL products or services. This information is provided through the use of third party service providers via web links.
By accessing these links, you will be leaving ESL Federal Credit Union's website and entering a website hosted by another party. ESL is not responsible for the content of this third party website. ESL does not represent either the third party or the member if the two enter into a transaction.
Please be advised that you will no longer be subject to, or under the protection of, the privacy and security policies of ESL Federal Credit Union. You are encouraged to review the privacy and security policies of the site you are entering, which may be different than those of ESL.
ContinueCancel
About Us
Customer Service
Call us at 585.336.1000
Comments & Questions
Find an ATM or Branch
Home
About Us
Privacy
Your privacy is important to us.  You have the right to control whether we share some of your personal information.
Want to change your privacy preferences?
Call us at 585.336.1000 or 800.848.2265.
Opt-out Form
Privacy Policy Important Privacy Choices for Consumers You have the right to control whether we share some of your personal information. Please read the following information carefully before making your choices. Your Rights You have the right to restrict the sharing of personal and financial information with our affiliates (companies we own or control) and outside companies that we do business with. This includes sending you information about other products or services. You may not limit the sharing of your personal and financial information for our everyday business purposes or as required by law. To read or receive our Privacy Notice
Download our Privacy Notice (PDF) Connect with us so we can help. California Privacy Notice (for California residents)
To limit the use of your ESL Information To limit the use of your ESL Information, complete our Privacy Opt Out Election form and submit electronically. You may also print the form and mail the completed form to us. If you have already completed the Privacy Opt Out Election form, you don't need to complete another one. Your preferences will remain the same until you tell us otherwise.
Online Practices ESL Federal Credit Union recognizes the importance of maintaining a presence on the World Wide Web for informational and e-commerce purposes in both attracting new members and retaining existing members. For the purpose of this statement, online activity is defined as the ability of members to access personal account information and general credit union information, to initiate transactions on your credit union accounts, and to apply for additional credit union products and services online. Our privacy policy is the same whether you are online or not. Information We Gather Online We may gather information on how a visitor navigates through the site and areas in which they show interest. We may also gather information such as number of visits to the site, page visits, and length of user sessions. This is similar to a traffic report: it tracks trends and behaviors of members/users in general, but does not identify individuals in particular. We use this information to better serve you and it helps keep our site relevant and useful by helping us understand what information users want. ESL uses Google Analytics as a tool to gather such information. To understand how ESL uses Google Analytics on esl.org, refer to:
https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites Our Use of Cookies ESL websites use a variety of cookies. Cookies are small plain text files sent by a website to a visitor’s device where they are stored in browser directories for varying lengths of time. They are often used to help users navigate websites more efficiently. Disabling cookies may prevent users from accessing some of the features on our websites as they may be necessary to certain functionality. A few examples of how cookies may be used:
Cookies remember choices you make when you use our websites. This provides you with a more personal experience and to avoid you having to re-select your preferences every time you visit our websites. Cookies collect information about visits to our websites and how users use/navigate our websites. Cookies track engagement with our content on or through social networking websites such as Facebook or Twitter. Cookies provide targeted advertising on other third-party websites based on the cookies that are placed on our websites.
To learn how to manage cookies and other browser settings, visit the browser’s support website:
Internet Explorer 11 (Microsoft) Edge (Microsoft) Safari 9 (Apple) Firefox (Mozilla) Chrome (Google)
Links to Other Non-ESL Websites ESL does offer links on our website to other vendors and third parties. These links are given to you to provide opportunity for you to take advantage of their products or services. ESL cannot guarantee how these third parties collect or use personally identifiable information about you. ESL does not represent either the third party or the member if the two enter into a transaction.
Third-Party Link Disclaimer For your convenience esl.org provides a variety of information on our web site that is not directly related to ESL products or services. This information is provided through the use of third party service providers via web links. By accessing these links you will be leaving ESL Federal Credit Union's web site and entering a web site hosted by another party. ESL is not responsible for the content of this third party web site. ESL does not represent either the third party or the member if the two enter into a transaction. Please be advised that you will no longer be subject to, or under the protection of, the privacy and security policies of ESL Federal Credit Union. You are encouraged to review the privacy and security policies of the site you are entering, which may be different than those of ESL.
Additional Information
Fraud Prevention
Security
Business Security Tips
Online banking makes transfers, payments, and automatic savings convenient for you.Sign up today
Thinking about your future?
For Personal:
Apple Personal Mobile App
Android Personal Mobile App
For Business:
225 Chestnut Street, Rochester NY 14604 Privacy Policy | Disclosures | Security
ESL, TEL-E$L, and CheckOK are registered service marks of ESL Federal Credit Union. Membership is subject to eligibility.
Secure Site
Equal Housing Lender Federally insured by the NCUA
Back to Top
